dailymedicalcases.net 2017-12-24

# Privacy Policy - DailyMedicalCases.net

DailyMedicalCases.net understand and respect your concern about your privacy, the security of your personal information is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used, and disclosed by DailyMedicalCases.net

_Sponsored Advertisement_  

**Personal Information**  
DailyMedicalCases.net is not interested in and does not collect any sensitive personal information from users of this site other than the usual information contained in server logs.

**Cookies**  
When you visit the DailyMedicalCases.net, our website sends your computer a cookie, which is a small file that resides on your computer’s hard drive and contains non-personally identifiable information about the user. Cookies allow DailyMedicalCases.net to make its website more useful by storing information about your preferences (your language preference, websites you have shorted recently etc). Also cookies are used from third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

**IP address and logging**  
Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc).

**Agreement with DailyMedicalCases.net policies**  
By accessing and/or using any of the DailyMedicalCases.net, you signify your understanding of and agreement with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our policies, please do not access or use our website.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “last modified” date at the top of this page. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how DailyMedicalCases.net protects your information.

**Contact**  
You can contact us with regard to this Privacy Policy using our [contact form](http://www.dailymedicalcases.net/contact-us/).

_This statement was last updated September 14, 2016._

_Sponsored Advertisement_
